Guide to the John H. Eyer Papers
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- John H. Eyer papers, 1930-1986; 1950-1974; 3932-001; 18.24 cubic feet (16 boxes) plus 1 oversize folder
  - PAPER WORKER UNION LOCALS, 1943-1972; SERIES 1 (Box-folder 1/1-5/18, Oversize folder 1)
    - Sitka, Alaska, Local 962: Legislation, Collective Bargaining, Picket Rules, Union Training, 1960-1965 (Box-folder 4/3)
    - Sitka, Alaska, Local 962: Health and Welfare Benefits, 1959-1963 (Box-folder 4/4)
    - Sitka, Alaska, Local 962 (Silver Bay), 1960-1965 (Box-folder 4/5)
    - Sitka, Alaska, Sitka Pulp Mill Builders: Agreement and Lunch Break and Overtime Issues, 1959 (Box-folder 4/6)
    - Sitka, Alaska, Alaska Lumber and Pulp Company: Group Insurance, 1960 (Box-folder 4/7)
    - Sitka, Alaska, Alaska Lumber and Pulp Company: Health Insurance Plans, 1954-1961 (Box-folder 4/8)
    - South Gate, California, South Gate Fibreboard Plant and Local 253: Wildcat Strike, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 4/9)
    - South Gate, California, Local 253: Fibreboard Wildcat Strike, Officers List, Trainings, 1959-1970 (Box-folder 4/10)
    - South Gate, California, International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers Local 253: Converters Workers Resolution to Become Western States Converters Association, 1960 January 14 (Box-folder 4/11)
    - Springfield, Oregon, Weyerhaeuser Company and Local 677: Collective Bargaining and Agreement Settlement, 1969 (Box-folder 4/12)
    - Springfield, Oregon, Local 677: Job Analysis, Seniority, Meeting Minutes, Taft-Hartley Compliance, 1957-1969 (Box-folder 4/13)
    - Steilacoom, Washington, West Tacoma Newsprint Company and Local 180: 4 July 1968 Holiday Work List Grievance, Minutes (Box-folder 4/14)
    - Steilacoom, Washington, West Tacoma Newsprint Company Ground Rules and Guidelines, 1963 (Box-folder 4/15)
    - Stockton, California, Local 320: Officers, Arbitration, Strike Fund, Lithographers, 1957-1971 (Box-folder 4/16)
    - Sumner, Washington, Fibreboard Corporation and Local 28: Grievances and Arbitration, 1966-1970 (Box-folder 4/17-18)
    - Sumner, Washington, Fibreboard Paper Products Corporation and Local 28: Seniority, Ground Rules and Related Grievances, 1964-1966 (Box-folder 4/19)
    - Sunnyside, Oregon, Local 717: Arbitration with Marathon Corporation, 1960 (Box-folder 4/20)
    - Sunnyside, Oregon, Local 717: Marathon Corporation Contract Negotiations, National Labor Relations Board (NLRB) Petitions, Elections, 1951-1964 (Box-folder 4/21)
    - Sunnyside, Washington, Local 717: Marathon Corporation Contract Negotiations, 1953 (Box-folder 4/22)
    - Tacoma, Washington, Plasticell Local 199: Union Training, 1956 (Box-folder 4/23)
    - Tacoma, Washington, Locals 237 and 180: Grievances and Arbitration, Strike, Observation Report, 1957-1970 (Box-folder 4/24)
    - Toledo, Oregon, Georgia-Pacific Corporation, Locals 13, 891, and 724: Job Analysis, Uniform Labor Agreement, Seniority, Pension, Elections, 1956-1971 (Box-folder 4/25)
    - Toledo, Oregon, Georgia-Pacific Corporation and Local 13: Apprenticeship Program, Grievances, Bargaining, 1959-1970 (Box-folder 4/26)
    - Toledo, Oregon, Georgia-Pacific Corporation and Local 13: Uniform Labor Agreement and Arbitration, 1966-1970 (Box-folder 4/27)
    - Toledo, Oregon, Georgia-Pacific Corporation Management Agenda and Contract Drafts, circa 1960-1969 (Box-folder 4/28)
    - Toledo, Oregon, Georgia-Pacific and Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers Local 13: Correspondence, Reports, Agreements, Notes, circa 1968-1969 (Box-folder 5/1)
    - Toledo, Oregon, Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers Local 13: Labor Agreement with Georgia-Pacific, circa 1951-1969 (Box-folder 5/2)
    - Vancouver, British Columbia, Local 433: Pacific Mills and Canadian Boxes Strike, 1951 (Box-folder 5/3)
    - Vancouver, Washington, Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers Local 171: Job Analysis, Strike, and NLRB Case, 1952-1967 (Box-folder 5/4)
    - Vancouver, Washington, Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers Locals 171 and 293: Correspondence, 1958-1962 (Box-folder 5/5)
    - Vancouver, Washington, Kieckhefer Company Milk Bottle Plant, circa 1951-1965 (Box-folder 5/6)
    - Vancouver, Washington, International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers Bemis Local 600: Strike, Negotiations, and Events, 1958-1965 (Box-folder 5/7)
    - Vancouver, Washington, International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers Bemis Local 600: Contract Negotiations, Holiday Pay, 1951-1954 (Box-folder 5/8)
    - Wallula and Pasco, Washington, International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers Locals 896 and 990: Elections, Officer's Training, Membership, 1959-1962 (Box-folder 5/9)
    - Wallula, Washington, Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers Local 69: Scab List, Arbitration, 1964-1967 (Box-folder 5/10)
    - Wauna, Oregon and Organizing at Crown Mill: Election and NLRB Case, 1965-1967 (Box-folder 5/11-14)
    - Wauna, Oregon and Organizing at Crown Mill: NLRB Case Court Papers, 1965 (Box-folder 5/15)
    - Wenatchee, Washington, International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers Local 784 and Pacific Pulp Molding Company, 1959-1964 (Box-folder 5/16)
    - Wenatchee, Washington, Pacific Pulp Molding Company and Local 784: Health and Welfare Fund, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 5/17)
    - West Linn, Oregon, West Linn Mill of Crown Zellerbach and Local 68 Negotiations, 1969 (Box-folder 5/18)
  - INTERNATIONAL BROTHERHOOD OF PULP, SULPHITE AND PAPER MILL WORKERS, 1950-1972; SERIES 2 (Box-folder 5/19-6/14,Oversize folder 1)
    Contains correspondence to and from local and International officers of the IBPSandPMW; correspondence, meeting minutes, photographs, publications, and other records from conventions, conferences, and executive board meetings; Local 242 Secretary Francis Hannigan and International Vice President John Sherman correspondence records; company contracts; and other assorted records documenting activities of the International.
    - Officer Correspondence, 1954-1972; Subseries A (Box-folder 5/19-38)
      - Correspondence Between George Brooks and Orville Braaten: Pension Plan, Contract Clauses, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 5/19)
      - Correspondence Between International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers International Officers and Locals, 1957-1962 (Box-folder 5/20)
      - International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers: Correspondence from George Brooks to R. D. Bradford, 1957-1959 (Box-folder 5/21)
      - International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers Correspondence: Acting President-Secretary William H. Burnell to Officers and Local Membership, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 5/22)
      - International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers Correspondence: Representative Robert Hetherington, 1957-1963 (Box-folder 5/23)
      - International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers Correspondence: International Representative Carol R. Howes, 1959-1966 (Box-folder 5/24)
      - International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers Correspondence: Ivor D. Isaacson, John Eyer, and George Brooks, 1957-1961 (Box-folder 5/25)
      - International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers Correspondence: International Representative Millard J. Lamb, 1960 (Box-folder 5/26)
      - International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers Correspondence: Vice President Oren Parker, 1959-1964 (Box-folder 5/27)
      - International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers Correspondence: International Representative A. Price, circa 1959-1961 (Box-folder 5/28)
      - International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers Correspondence: Vice President John Sherman, 1957-1965 (Box-folder 5/29)
      - International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers Correspondence: Assorted, 1959-1963 (Box-folder 5/30)
      - International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers International Staff: Correspondence and News Clippings, 1954-1960 (Box-folder 5/31)
      - International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers British Columbia Staff: Correspondence, 1957-1964; Contains British Columbian Convention delegate photograph and issue of Western Pulp and Paper Worker, March 1959. (Box-folder 5/32)
      - International Brotherhood of Pulp. Sulphite, and Paper Mill Workers Research and Education Department Correspondence, 1956-1959 (Box-folder 5/33)
      - Correspondence to and from George W. Brooks, 1955-1971 (Box-folder 5/34)
      - American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) Correspondence, 1960-1961, 1972; Some documents relate to the Alaska Employees Retirement Act. (Box-folder 5/35)
      - Correspondence Between John Eyer and International Officers, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 5/36)
      - Reactions to Visitation of International Representative Jerald Hatt to Local 153 in Longview, Washington, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 5/37)
      - Albany, Oregon, Local 824: Correspondence to President John Burke from Local Secretary Edward D. Foley, 1963 December 30 (Box-folder 5/38)
    - Meetings and Conventions, 1951-1965; Subseries B (Box-folder 5/39-6/3)
      - 25th Convention of the International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, Montreal, Quebec, 1959 (Box-folder 5/39)
      - International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers Pre-Wage Conference, 1951 (Box-folder 5/40)
      - International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers Conventions: Transcripts, Minutes, Delegate Roll Call Form, and News Clippings, 1959-1963 (Box-folder 5/41)
      - International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers Minutes of the International Executive Board Meeting, 1963 January 14-17 (Box-folder 5/42)
      - Annual Labor Management Safety Conference Correspondence and Photographs, 1955-1959; Includes photographs of John Eyer. (Box-folder 5/43)
      - Labor-Management Safety Program Planning Committee and Safety Conferences, 1956-1965 (Box-folder 5/44)
      - International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers and Washington Safety Code, 1959 (Box-folder 6/1)
      - British Columbia Locals: Health and Welfare Survey, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 6/2)
      - British Columbia International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers Strike, 1957-1958; Contains issues of Paper Worker, November 1957-January 1958 and Western Pulp and Paper Worker, January and March 1958 (Box-folder 6/3)
    - Secretary Francis Hannigan, Local 242 (Portland, OR), 1950-1964; Subseries C (Box-folder 6/4-6)
      - Independent Paper Stock Company Union Contract, 1950-1962 (Box-folder 6/4)
      - Correspondence to and from International Officers, 1957-1964 (Box-folder 6/5)
      - Local 242 Registration with the National Labor Relations Board, 1952-1959 (Box-folder 6/6)
    - Vice President John Sherman, 1951-1963; Subseries D (Box-folder 6/7-10)
      - Correspondence to and from John Sherman and Other Officers, 1951-1959 (Box-folder 6/7)
      - Rose City Paper Products Company Contract: Correspondence with Management, 1952-1960 (Box-folder 6/8)
      - Fibreboard Paper Products, Portland Plant: Wage Rates and Seniority Roster, 1959-1963 (Box-folder 6/9)
      - Pacific Paper Materials Company Contract: Letter to Company Vice President from John Sherman, 1952 March 21 (Box-folder 6/10)
    - Other Records, 1952-1964; Subseries E (Box-folder 6/11-14, Oversize folder 1)
      - John P. Burke Scholarship Award, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 6/11)
      - Revised Field Manual Notice, 1964 March 3 (Box-folder 6/12)
      - Executive Board Reports and International and Local Officers Lists, 1955-1964 (Box-folder 6/13)
      - Visits from International Labor Leaders to Portland, Oregon, 1952-1956; Contains photographs of labor leaders visiting from the Philippines. (Box-folder 6/14)
      - Oversized Signs, Flyers, and Publications, 1956-1970 (Folder:oversize 1)
        - "Truth for Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers" Newspapers, Volume 1, Numbers 1-2, 1961; Retaliatory newspaper siding with the International in response to the Rank and File Movement for Democratic Action.
  - ASSOCIATION OF WESTERN PULP AND PAPER WORKERS, 1952-1972; SERIES 3 (Box-folder 6/15-8/22, Oversize folder 1)
    Contains assorted records from the AWPPW, including officer and committee correspondence and reports; meeting minutes; material related to collective bargaining, negotiations, and the Uniform Labor Agreement; arbitration and grievances; officer elections, speeches given, and voting on constitutional changes and local union resolutions at conventions; reports and correspondence from regional councils, including a series specific to the activities of Representative John R. Swanson of the Northern Washington and Alaska Area Council; union publications; records related to attempts of the AWPPW to organize in the Southeast region of the U.S.; officer rosters; and other records related to AWPPW activities.
    - Correspondence and Reports, 1965-1972; Subseries A (Box-folder 6/15-27)
      - University of Wisconsin School for Workers: Correspondence between Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers and Professor George Hagglund, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 6/15)
      - Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers President Correspondence and Reports, 1966-1972 (Box-folder 6/16-17)
      - Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers Secretary Treasurer's Correspondence and Reports, 1967-1972 (Box-folder 6/18)
      - Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers General Vice President Correspondence and Reports, 1967-1972 (Box-folder 6/19)
      - Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers President's Correspondence and Reports, 1965-1972 (Box-folder 6/20)
      - Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers Executive Vice President Dick archer: Correspondence and Reports, 1966-1972 (Box-folder 6/21-22)
      - Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers General Vice President John Eyer's Notes, Correspondence, and Reports, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 6/23)
      - Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers Assorted Correspondence, 1968-1972 (Box-folder 6/24)
      - Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers and 4-Union Coordinating Committee: Minutes and Correspondence, 1965-1968 (Box-folder 6/25)
      - Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers Legal Correspondence, 1966-1970 (Box-folder 6/26-27)
    - Collective Bargaining, 1967-1972; Subseries B (Box-folder 6/28-32)
      - Memorandum to Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers Regarding Local Bargaining, 1967 November 16 (Box-folder 6/28)
      - Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers Negotiations and Strike, 1969 (Box-folder 6/29-30)
      - Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers Uniform Labor Agreement and Collective Bargaining, 1972 (Box-folder 6/31)
      - Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers Collective Bargaining Committee Report: Uniform Labor Agreement vs Independent Locals, 1968 (Box-folder 6/32)
    - Regional Councils, 1959-1972; Subseries C (Box-folder 7/1-14)
      - Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers Western Oregon Area Representative: Reports and Correspondence, 1965-1972 (Box-folder 7/1)
      - Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers Northern California Area Council: Reports and Correspondence, 1965-1970 (Box-folder 7/2)
      - Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers Southern California Area Council: Reports and Correspondence, 1959-1970 (Box-folder 7/3)
      - Southern Washington Area Council Correspondence and Reports, 1966-1970 (Box-folder 7/4)
      - Southern Washington Area Council Reports, 1965-1968 (Box-folder 7/5)
      - Southern Washington Area Council Weekly Reports, 1970 (Box-folder 7/6)
      - Northern Washington and Alaska Area Council of Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers: Correspondence and Reports, 1967-1972; Folder 7 contains information about the gender pay gap. (Box-folder 7/7-8)
      - Northwestern Washington Area Council of Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers: 2nd Quarter Reports, 1972 (Box-folder 7/9)
      - Southern California Area Council of Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers: Reports and Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 7/10)
      - Northern California Area Council of Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers: Reports and Correspondence, 1967-1968; Contains information about the gender pay gap. (Box-folder 7/11)
      - Oregon Area Council of Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers: Reports and Correspondence, 1967-1972 (Box-folder 7/12)
      - Southern Washington Area Council of Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers: Reports and Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 7/13)
      - Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers, Equal Employment Opportunity Commission, and Gender-Based Discrimination, 1962-1967 (Box-folder 7/14)
    - Conventions, 1964-1972; Subseries D (Box-folder 7/15-7/26)
      - Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers President William R. Perrin's Address at LSW Convention, Spokane, Washington, 1967 (Box-folder 7/15)
      - Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers Convention: Budget, Correspondence, Minutes, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 7/16)
      - Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers: Constitution Committee Meeting Report, 1964 (Box-folder 7/17)
      - Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers Convention: Presidential Address, Committees, Ballot, Resolutions, 1966 (Box-folder 7/18)
      - Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers Convention: Speech Drafts, Correspondence, Resolutions, Committees, 1967 (Box-folder 7/19)
      - Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers Convention: Reports, Correspondence, Constitutional Changes, and Resolutions, 1969 (Box-folder 7/20)
      - Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers Convention Staff Meeting: Constitutional Changes and Local Union Resolutions, 1969 (Box-folder 7/21)
      - Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers 5th Convention Referendum Election Results, 1970 (Box-folder 7/22)
      - Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers Convention: Ballot Measures, 1971 (Box-folder 7/23)
      - Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers Convention: Articles of Confederation, Congressman Lloyd Meeds Speech, 1972 (Box-folder 7/24)
      - Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers Conventions: Resolutions, Committee Reports, Proposed Constitution, circa 1965-1972 (Box-folder 7/25)
      - Northern California Council of Pulp and Paper Workers Resolutions to Constitution Convention, 1967 October 27 (Box-folder 7/26)
    - Representative John R. Swanson, Northern Washington and Alaska Area Council, 1952-1972; Subseries E (Box-folder 7/27-8/4)
      - Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers Oregon City Locals 68 and 166: Correspondence, 1967-1972 (Box-folder 7/27)
      - Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers Longview, Washington Locals: Correspondence, 1963-1970 (Box-folder 7/28)
      - Ketchikan Pulp Company Labor Agreement, circa 1970 (Box-folder 7/29)
      - Ketchikan, Alaska Locals: Correspondence, Employee Data, Legal Case Files, 1967-1972 (Box-folder 7/30)
      - Ketchikan, Alaska Locals: 1970 Strike and Grievances, 1968-1972 (Box-folder 7/31)
      - News Clippings on Paper Workers in Ketchikan, Alaska, 1957-1967 (Box-folder 7/32)
      - Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers Local 22, Kent, Washington: Policies, Negotiations, Wage Rates, 1972 (Box-folder 7/33)
      - Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers Local 169, Grays Harbor Paper Company, Hoquiam, Washington: Correspondence and Grievances, 1956-1972 (Box-folder 7/34)
      - Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers Local 169, Grays Harbor Paper Company, Hoquiam, Washington: Arbitration and Grievances, Correspondence, Rosters, 1966-1971 (Box-folder 8/1)
      - Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers Clerical Local 315, Hoquiam, Washington: Rosters, Correspondence, Agreements, 1965-1971 (Box-folder 8/2)
      - Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers Local 180, West Tacoma Newsprint Company, Steilacoom, Washington: Arbitration and Grievances, Correspondence, Minutes, 1952-1969 (Box-folder 8/3)
      - Weyerhaeuser Company and Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers Negotiations, 1969 (Box-folder 8/4)
    - Other Records, 1964-1972; Subseries F (Box-folder 8/5-22)
      - Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers Executive Board Records, 1965-1969 (Box-folder 8/5)
      - Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers Local 171 Trial Board Hearing Proceedings, 1965 December 14 (Box-folder 8/6)
      - Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers: Organizing in Southeastern United States, 1964-1967 (Box-folder 8/7-8)
      - Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers and International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers Conflict, 1966-1967; Contains three photographs from breakfast meeting in July 1966 in Tacoma with President Boyd DeAndrade of the Pressmans Union who brought the offer of a Federal Charter under the AFL-CIO to the Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers. (Box-folder 8/9)
      - Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers and Pacific Coast Association of Pulp and Paper Manufacturers: Title VII and Women Paperworkers, 1966-1968 (Box-folder 8/10)
      - Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers Company Coordinating Committees: Pensions, 1966-1968 (Box-folder 8/11)
      - Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers Health and Welfare: Sick Pay Policies, 1966-1968 (Box-folder 8/12)
      - Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers Coastwide Election, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 8/13)
      - Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers Election, 1965 (Box-folder 8/14)
      - 1964 Strike Between Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers and Pacific Coast Association of Pulp and Paper Manufacturers, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 8/15)
      - Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers Public Review Board Cases, 1966-1972 (Box-folder 8/16)
      - Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers and Retroactive Pay Trial, 1964-1966 (Box-folder 8/17)
      - Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers: "Continuous Tabulation of Executive Policies and Actions" Revisions, 1966-1972 (Box-folder 8/18)
      - Pulp and Paperworkers of Canada, 1968-1969; Contains issue of The Leaflet, May 1969 (Box-folder 8/19)
      - Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers Press Releases, 1967-1968; Contains information about gender and pay equality. (Box-folder 8/20)
      - Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers Officers Lists, circa 1966-1967 (Box-folder 8/21)
      - Pasco, Washington, Local 69: Correspondence, Officers Rosters, 1968-1972 (Box-folder 8/22)
      - Oversized Signs, Flyers, and Publications, 1956-1970 (Folder:oversize 1)
        - Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers Ballot of Proposed Constitutional Changes, 1970 November 2-8
  - UNITED PAPERMAKERS AND PAPERWORKERS, 1958-1969; SERIES 4 (Box-folder 8/23-27, Oversize folder 1)
    Contains officer correspondence, publications, handwritten sign advertising a meeting, and other records related to the activities of the United Papermakers and Paperworkers, including the Pulp and Paper Workers of Canada, as well as a file related to efforts of the Teamsters to organize paperworkers.
    - Correspondence to and from United Papermakers and Paperworkers Vice President and Regional Director Al E. Brown, 1958-1961 (Box-folder 8/23)
    - Pulp and Paper Workers of Canada, 1962-1969 (Box-folder 8/24)